This is Khun Chai Phakdee.
From now on, he will be your fiancé.
Greetings, Lady Rinkham.
My name is Phakdee.
Dad, are you trying to force me into an arranged marriage? I won't accept this.
What did you just say?
I do not accept this engagement.
I refuse.
You are being impolite.
But I never asked you to control my life, Dad.
I have already made up my mind about this.
I want to find someone to take care of you.
But I already have Kaew.
Kaew won't be with you forever, Rinkham.
But I haven't chosen yet.
But you ought to know your duty.
I know it well,
and I will choose for myself who I love
and want to marry.
Not have you chosen for me, Dad.
But you ought to know your duty.
I know it well,
and I will choose for myself who I love
and want to marry.
Not have you chosen for me, Dad.
Rinkham...
I can't accept this.
I don't want a life like that.
I want to choose the person I love myself
and I already know who that is.
Then what are you going to do?
I'll make dad see
that I'm completely unfit to be a bride for anyone he picks.
If that "Khun Chai" guy can tolerate me, then let him try!
Rinkham, come here for a moment, my child.
I’m going outside with Kaew.
But I have something to…
Let’s save it for another day, sir.
Around that time, she was very close with those guards, wasn't she?
Yes, sir.
Why do you come to the market every day?
I don't want to go back home to see my dad.
I’ve figured out what we should do!
Is this piece good?
Let's choose for yourself.
I want you to choose it,
because sometimes… you are the one who has to take it off.
This color suits you.
I don't need to…
Want to try it on?
I am a guard.
I don't need to wear this.
What are you doing to Rinkham?!
Rinkham!
Don't move.
You have great taste, my lady.
Here, turn around and let me see.
It’s not the kind of clothing I’m used to wearing.
My lady, your guard is blushing.
I've never seen you like this before.
And you shouldn't be seeing it either.
But I think it's beautiful.
That's enough.
Not yet. Turn around one more time.
Rinkham...
You should wear things like this more often.
Never.
Auntie, aren't those two acting way too close for master and servant?
That's what I'm saying.
I wonder if they're guards and masters, or actually lovers.
They don't look like a master and servant at all.
This really isn't proper.
Hey.
My Lady.
Please don't cause a scene.
I beg you.
Let's go back, My Lady.
I don't want to go home yet, Kaew.
Your dad will get worried.
You two sure are close.
I heard people in the market gossiping about it...
Master and servant, or something more?
And what does that have to do with you?
I just don't like seeing things that are unnatural.
because soon enough, certain important people might start getting upset about it.
If so, then don't look.
You got a big mouth!
It seems you are the one acting out of line right now.
Stay away from her.
Otherwise, I might not be this kind next time.
Alright, alright.
Are you angry?
I just don't like anyone speaking about you like that.
No matter what the truth may be.
But I like it when you protect me.
Or should I let him say it again?
So you can protect me one more time.
Rinkham.
I'm just kidding.
But I really do like it when you protect me, you know.
You are quite charming.
Let us return, My Lady.